# **KAUSHIK DANGE**

# Frontend Angular Software Developer

- @www.linkedin.com/in/kaushik-dange-a39b9944

#### SUMMARY

Experienced Angular Developer with 8 months of experience and a degree in Information Technology. Expert in Angular with experience in versions above Angular 10. Skilled in HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript, Typescript, Material UI, Angular and Agile methodologies.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Software Engineer

08/2022 - 03/2023

#### Siemens Technology and Services Pvt Ltd.

Pune, Maharashtra

Developing and maintaining web application using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript and Angular.

- Developed and maintained responsive web applications using Angular Framework.
- Integrated RESTful API's and third party libraries to enhance application functionality.
- Implemented responsive design using HTML and CSS resulting in increase in user engagement.
- Collaborating with cross-functional teams to gather requirements, design, develop and test web applications.

# **Customer Service Associate**

12/2021 - 03/2022

# Grey Knight Services Pvt Ltd.

Solapur

Provided excellent customer service to improve business performance.

- Provides excellent customer and product service; ensured customer are satisfied.
- Manages weekly and monthly reporting to the Customer Service Department.
- Work closely with team and supervisors to meet weekly and monthly production goals.

# **Customer Engagement**

08/2018 - 07/2020

#### Mahindra Integrated Business Solutions

Solapur

Provide excellent customer service to improve business performance.

- Understand customer requirements to provide appropriate clarifications and solutions.
- Contribute Ideas to resolve customer problems to improve productivity.
- Maintain broad knowledge of customer products and services.

#### **EDUCATION**

# Bachelor of Engineering (B.E) in Information Technology

2011 - 2014

Bharati Vidyapeeth's College of Engineering

Kolhapur

#### LANGUAGES

English Native •••• Hindi Native ••••
Marathi Native ••••

# CERTIFICATION

Angular - The Complete Guide (2023 Edition) from Udemy



#### **STRENGTHS**

# Problem-solving

Strong problem solving skills by effectively identifying and analyzing complex issues within Frontend.

#### ★ Communication

Collaborated with cross-functional teams to ensure successful project completion.

#### **SKILLS**

 $\mathsf{HTML} \cdot \mathsf{CSS} \cdot \mathsf{Bootstrap} \cdot \mathsf{JavaScript} \cdot$ 

TypeScript · Material UI · Angular · SQL ·

GIT · Jira

#### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

- Participated State Level
  Technical Event in "Code
  Shuffle" at KITCOE, Kolhapur
  C-Programming
- Participated State Level
   Technical Event in
   "Counter-Strike" game at
   SESP, Solapur.

# PERSONAL PROJECTS

Secured 3rd position.

#### **E-Commerce**

SignUp & Login for Seller and User. Seller can add & view products, where user can view product can add product to cart, buy products, search product,etc

#### **Messaging Application**

It is used for send messages from one logged in user to another user. The logged in user can chat with other users and can view chat history

#### PERSONAL INFORMATION

Date of Birth: 31-July-1993

Martial Status: Single

Notice Period: Immediate Joiner

Experience: 3 years